Oak Teppaitoon

AUSTRALIAN CITIZEN
0406 975 950
Oak.teppaitoon@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Results-driven professional with exceptional communication and customer focus. Strong analytical and problem-solving skills. Advanced computer skills, SQL, and Python, Expert in Microsoft Excel and VBA. **Tableau Desktop Certified Associate** and **AWS Certified Machine Learning Specialty**.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

SCHIAVELLO GROUP a top 100 Australian private company built on quality, service excellence and innovation, has been creating and servicing world-class work and living environments for over 50 years.

Configuration Officer/Business System Analyst

February 2017 – Present

- Product Configurator
 - o End to end SDLC of product configurator to automatically create Bill of Materials (BOM) and Routings (Labour) based on users' inputs.
 - Data analysis of products and build models to best suit business needs.
- Automatic Configurator Tester
 - Develop an automatic tester to batch test product configurator.
 - Test and track any change in price and pinpoint where the source of change occurs.
- Business System Analyst
 - Drive the change to improve capability and efficiency of the application and business system in an Agile development environment.
 - Create SSRS reports for business unit including Manufacturing order and Factory loading report, Cost and Margin analysis, Products Sales analysis.
 - o Troubleshoot, debug and support users with issues related to business system.

MASKOFF EVENTS a leading event organiser in Thai community in Victoria. Collaborated annually with Thai Culture and Food Festival held at Federation Square (the world's second biggest Thai Culture and Food Festival).

Production Supervisor

July 2014 – October 2016

- Prepared cost estimates, analysed customer requirements and consulted with project managers.
- Provided technical troubleshooting and problem solving for clients with equipment/system issues.

BALLARAT VIBRATED CONCRETE INDUSTRIES (BVCI) specialise in the development, manufacture and distribution of plastic polymer and pre-cast concrete cable jointing pits and pit access covers.

Master Production Scheduler

October 2013 – May 2014

- Managed production schedule for Plastic division and Concrete division worth \$55,000 every day.
- Calculated factory work load & production capacity based on available labour (total of 35-40 FTE).
- Reviewed and analysed demand management, staffing and inventory.

Production Engineer/Procurement Officer – Concrete Division

March 2012 – September 2013

- Co-managed special order projects including HV pit worth \$1.7 Million, road barrier worth \$360,000.
- Analysed statistical sales, forecast and production data, prepared and maintained production reports.
- Analysed and planned for purchasing of long lead time products from overseas based on sales statistic, sales forecast, project demand, and inventory level.
- Developed Production Planner Excel tool to effectively manage production scheduling.

JATCO ENGINEERING expert in crane inspection, certification, maintenance and servicing.

Administrative Assistant (Short term replacement)

July 2011 - December 2011

- Provided assistance to mechanics, prepared service report for crane repairs and inspections.
- Issued purchase orders, performed job safety analysis.

Oak Teppaitoon

AUSTRALIAN CITIZEN 0406 975 950 Oak.teppaitoon@gmail.com

SPRAYING SYSTEMS CO PTY LTD a world leading in spray technology, manufacturer of industrial spray products including air control nozzles, tank washers, automated spray systems and controls.

Sales Engineer

August 2008 – June 2011

- Building and maintaining customer base in Tasmania and South Australia region.
- Designed and made recommendations to customers in various industries.
- Increased sales year-over-year (12% increase in 2009 and 10% increase in 2010)

EDUCATION & PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

AWS

Certified Machine Learning Specialty
Certified Developer - Associate

Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

March 2020

January 2020

December 2019

Tableau

Tableau Desktop Certified Associate October 2019

Udemy

Tableau 10 Advanced Training

Python and Django web development

September 2019

May 2019 – June 2019

Microsoft Professional Program

Data Science September 2018 – May 2019

SkillSoft

Six Sigma Yellow Belt September 2016 – November 2016

Monash University

Bachelor of Engineering (Electrical & Computer Systems) March 2002 – November 2006

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- · Strong track record of business and technical problem solving
- Proven ability to learn new skills quickly
- Understanding of business needs and issues
- Strong written and verbal communication skills
- Great team player and knowledge sharing
- Six Sigma process improvement

COMPUTER AND PROGRAMING SKILLS

- Microsoft SQL server
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Power Point
- Microsoft Power BI
- Microsoft Azure Machine Learning
- SQL Server Reporting Services (SSRS)
- SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS)

- AWS Sagemaker
- Tableau
- Python
- Django
- HTML
- CSS

INTEREST

Manchester United, Sir Alex Ferguson, Coldplay, Watch Collecting, Continuous Learning, Technology and Environment.